<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AAA on Alvin McGee&#39;s Webpage</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/aaa/</link>
    <description>Recent content in AAA on Alvin McGee&#39;s Webpage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 16:56:38 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/humor/aaa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Assorted Awful Advice Part Seven: Applying for College</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/aaa/college/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/aaa/college/</guid>
      <description>Assorted Awful Advice Part Seven: Applying for College Anabel Lee is one of those people who advertises marketing courses on social media. After making a grand total of twenty five 25 dollars in the business last year, Lee decided to branch out into crypto trading, essential oils, and giving advice to people happier than she is. Based on that one semester she spent in community college, Lee has christened herself an expert on all things college, and has started selling courses on that too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assorted Awful Advice Part Six: Gomer&#39;s Guide to Christian Homeschooling</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/aaa/6---homeschooling/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/aaa/6---homeschooling/</guid>
      <description>Assorted Awful Advice Part Six: Gomer&amp;rsquo;s Guide to Christian Homeschooling Gomer Schmid is the submissive wife of Jebediah Schmid and stay at home mother of 17 children, all of whom they have homeschooled since birth. She previously worked part - time manufacturing essential oils and knee - length denim skirts. But then, her husband was fired, forcing her to stop working out of a fear that being the family&amp;rsquo;s breadwinner would compromise male headship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assorted Awful Advice Part Five: PC Care</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/aaa/5---pc-care/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/aaa/5---pc-care/</guid>
      <description>Assorted Awful Advice Part Five: PC Care Jeb Smutty is a 14 year old middle school student in Fort Worth, Texas, where he spends his days watching anime, browsing Reddit, and making life hell for his older sister, Kristie. Despite his young age, Smutty has gained quite a reputation for exacerbating technical difficulties and bemoaning his perpetual celibacy all across the internet. When we decided to host an article about computers, we knew he was just the man for the job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assorted Awful Advice Part Four: How to Become a Millionaire</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/aaa/4---millionaire/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/aaa/4---millionaire/</guid>
      <description>Assorted Awful Advice Part Four: How to Become a Millionaire Sleazy McFly is a well - known self help author and convicted con artist. About 70 people have bought his free book, and more than four of them didn&amp;rsquo;t try to sue him afterwards.
Hey there fellas, I&amp;rsquo;m Sleazy McFly, but you can call me Sleaze for short. I&amp;rsquo;m here to make you rich, and if you follow all of my advice down to the letter, I can confidently tell you that one of us will be richer than he was before!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assorted Awful Advice Part Three: Sleeping</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/aaa/3---sleeping/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/aaa/3---sleeping/</guid>
      <description>Assorted Awful Advice Part Three: Sleeping Dr. Jim Stanford is a well - known chiropractor and Scientologist, as well as the co - founder of Carl Robinson&amp;rsquo;s Association for Pediatric Studies. He was the only person with a &amp;ldquo;Dr.&amp;rdquo; next to their name who was willing to write something for us vaguely related to medicine, so we&amp;rsquo;re stuck with him.
I&amp;rsquo;m Dr. Jim Stanford (PhD), and I have some alarming news for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assorted Awful Advice Part Two: How to Get a Girlfriend</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/aaa/2---getting-a-girlfriend/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 21:09:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/aaa/2---getting-a-girlfriend/</guid>
      <description>Assorted Awful Advice Part Two: How to Get a Girlfriend This post is guest – written by Lester Phelps. Phelps is a burgeoning TikTok star and professional social media influencer. Since his rise to stardom last Tuesday, Phelps has helped at least three men just like you get laid, or so he claims on the ‘about’ section of his YouTube page. He lives in his parents’ basement in Boston, where he enjoys drinking Mountain Dew and browsing 4chan with the love of his life, a Sailor Moon bodypillow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assorted Awful Advice Part One: Driving</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/aaa/1---driving/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 11:05:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/aaa/1---driving/</guid>
      <description>Assorted Awful Advice Part One: Driving This post is guest - written by Zippity O&amp;rsquo;Neil, who has gained much notoriety as a collector of DUIs and parking tickets. Zippity lives in Birmingham, Alabama, where he can regularly be found borrowing money from loan sharks in order to pay his car insurance bills.
Hey, y&amp;rsquo;all, name&amp;rsquo;s Zippity, and I&amp;rsquo;m gonna learn you the right way to drive them cars. And I ain&amp;rsquo;t talking about that BS they teach youngins out them driving schools - I&amp;rsquo;m talking about the real deal.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>