<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Math Problems on Alvin McGee&#39;s Webpage</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/math-problems/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Math Problems on Alvin McGee&#39;s Webpage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/math-problems/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Epilogue: The Eschatological Victory of Jack</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/epilogue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/epilogue/</guid>
      <description>Epilogue: The Eschatological Victory of Jack Though the antichrist was able to render Jack unconscious and cast him into a coma, Pastor Jim and his armada of Florida men were able to prevail over the beast in the end. Having been defeated, Chase returned to Heck. But this time, as he had been the antichrist, he was numbered among the worst and gravest of sinners; leading to his imprisonment in the deepest and darkest pit of Heck.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Thirty-Nine: Cornpop is a Bad Dude</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/39/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/39/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Thirty-Nine: Cornpop is a Bad Dude Jack and his crew steal Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s fastest UFO and return once more to the Earth. They land on Jeffery Epstein&amp;rsquo;s island - now restored to its previous glory - to find Joe Biden and Bill Clinton standing in front of the door.
&amp;ldquo;What the hell kid?&amp;rdquo; asks Bill Clinton. &amp;ldquo;I thought you died!&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I was once slain, but now I live. I am Jack, conqueror of death!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Thirty-Eight: Tesla Man - Least of the Archons</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/38/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/38/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Thirty-Eight: Tesla Man - Least of the Archons At the crack of Philip&amp;rsquo;s whip, Star in the Morning Sky begins lumbering forwards on her borderline defunct legs. As she reaches 8.8 miles per hour, Jack and his company enter the tunnel of light once more. As they go forward, Jack ceases to be the disembodied ghost he has been, and finds himself arrayed as the god - emperor of mankind once more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Thirty-Seven: The Deepest Pit of Heck</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/37/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/37/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Thirty-Seven: The Deepest Pit of Heck Jack and his compatriots steel themselves for what&amp;rsquo;s ahead, for they know the next circle of Heck is deepest and darkest one, home to the greatest of sinners. It is the place where the soul Jack must rescue for his quest is said to dwell.
But, when they get there, they&amp;rsquo;re pleasantly surprised. It just looks like a bar. Some lit EDM beats are playing in the background, and the stench of beer can be detected everywhere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Thirty-Six: Two True Scotsmen</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/36/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/36/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Thirty-Six: Two True Scotsmen The next circle of Heck looks rather peaceful. When Jack first enters it, nothing seems out of the ordinary. All sees is a pot roasting over a campfire, around which sit Shrek and John Duns Scotus.
&amp;lsquo;Like zoinks!&amp;quot; exclaims Shaggy. &amp;ldquo;Shrek, I was your biggest fan! John Duns Scotus, you were incredibly influential on my understanding of the univocity of theological verbiage! What did you guys do to, like, get darned to Heck!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Thirty - Five: Demons are a Girl&#39;s Best Friend</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/35/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/35/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Thirty - Five: Demons are a Girl&amp;rsquo;s Best Friend As Jack and his ever expanding band of merry men journey their way into the new circle of heck, they hear millions of people throwing up as one. As they come within sight of the darned here, they see a huge mass of pregnant women, all of whom appear to be deep in the throes of morning sickness.
&amp;ldquo;Dear God!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Thirty-Three: Chase&#39;s Evergaol</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/33/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/33/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Thirty-Three: Chase&amp;rsquo;s Evergaol 🍺Listen to this song while working out the math problem, and you may escape the ghastly punishment forced upon Chase by the powers that be🇩🇪
Jack and his motley crew walk on into the next circle of Heck, which they know is now home to their old friend Chase. At first, it seems very pleasant. It just looks like a normal bar, though an impeccably clean one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Twenty-Nine: High School Faces Eternity</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/29/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/29/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Twenty-Nine: High School Faces Eternity Jack and his friends finally reach the other side of the black sea. Chocking through the stench, they see the portion of Heck reserved for stupid teenagers. Here are imprisoned all the people who tempted Bloddy Mary, engaged in street racing, listened to Stairway to Heaven backtracked, or made love in that one porta potty off of 494.
Their punishment is to forever be imprisoned within an enlarged version of the average public high school bathroom.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>