<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Alvin McGee&#39;s Webpage</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Alvin McGee&#39;s Webpage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 15:31:39 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/humor/math/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Epilogue: The Eschatological Victory of Jack</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/epilogue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/epilogue/</guid>
      <description>Epilogue: The Eschatological Victory of Jack Though the antichrist was able to render Jack unconscious and cast him into a coma, Pastor Jim and his armada of Florida men were able to prevail over the beast in the end. Having been defeated, Chase returned to Heck. But this time, as he had been the antichrist, he was numbered among the worst and gravest of sinners; leading to his imprisonment in the deepest and darkest pit of Heck.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Forty: It&#39;s the End of the Line of the Final Journey</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/40/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/40/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Forty: It&amp;rsquo;s the End of the Line of the Final Journey Jack and his friends run into Jeffery Epstein&amp;rsquo;s house, frantically searching for George Soros and Klaus Schwab - the last two of the archons.
&amp;ldquo;Wait,&amp;rdquo; says Philip, &amp;ldquo;I hear them on the balcony upstairs, the one overlooking the ocean! They&amp;rsquo;re talking in Latin, must be summoning the antichrist right now.&amp;rdquo;
They rush up the stairs like there&amp;rsquo;s no tomorrow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Thirty-Nine: Cornpop is a Bad Dude</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/39/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/39/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Thirty-Nine: Cornpop is a Bad Dude Jack and his crew steal Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s fastest UFO and return once more to the Earth. They land on Jeffery Epstein&amp;rsquo;s island - now restored to its previous glory - to find Joe Biden and Bill Clinton standing in front of the door.
&amp;ldquo;What the hell kid?&amp;rdquo; asks Bill Clinton. &amp;ldquo;I thought you died!&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I was once slain, but now I live. I am Jack, conqueror of death!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Thirty-Eight: Tesla Man - Least of the Archons</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/38/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/38/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Thirty-Eight: Tesla Man - Least of the Archons At the crack of Philip&amp;rsquo;s whip, Star in the Morning Sky begins lumbering forwards on her borderline defunct legs. As she reaches 8.8 miles per hour, Jack and his company enter the tunnel of light once more. As they go forward, Jack ceases to be the disembodied ghost he has been, and finds himself arrayed as the god - emperor of mankind once more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Thirty-Seven: The Deepest Pit of Heck</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/37/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/37/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Thirty-Seven: The Deepest Pit of Heck Jack and his compatriots steel themselves for what&amp;rsquo;s ahead, for they know the next circle of Heck is deepest and darkest one, home to the greatest of sinners. It is the place where the soul Jack must rescue for his quest is said to dwell.
But, when they get there, they&amp;rsquo;re pleasantly surprised. It just looks like a bar. Some lit EDM beats are playing in the background, and the stench of beer can be detected everywhere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intermission 3: A Cat that Really is Gone</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/37-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/37-5/</guid>
      <description>Intermission 3: A Cat that Really is Gone Jack and his friends now come to Satan’s throne room in the city of Pandaleerium, which was built to guard the gates of Heck against darned souls seeking to escape. But, Satan’s throne is empty. Beside it stands the goat demon Baphomet, who looks rather tired.
“What happened to Satan, man? I was looking forward to whipping his ass!” says Philip.
Baphomet sighs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Thirty-Six: Two True Scotsmen</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/36/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/36/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Thirty-Six: Two True Scotsmen The next circle of Heck looks rather peaceful. When Jack first enters it, nothing seems out of the ordinary. All sees is a pot roasting over a campfire, around which sit Shrek and John Duns Scotus.
&amp;lsquo;Like zoinks!&amp;quot; exclaims Shaggy. &amp;ldquo;Shrek, I was your biggest fan! John Duns Scotus, you were incredibly influential on my understanding of the univocity of theological verbiage! What did you guys do to, like, get darned to Heck!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Thirty - Five: Demons are a Girl&#39;s Best Friend</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/35/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/35/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Thirty - Five: Demons are a Girl&amp;rsquo;s Best Friend As Jack and his ever expanding band of merry men journey their way into the new circle of heck, they hear millions of people throwing up as one. As they come within sight of the darned here, they see a huge mass of pregnant women, all of whom appear to be deep in the throes of morning sickness.
&amp;ldquo;Dear God!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Thirty-Four: Of Grindr and Meat Grinder</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/34/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/34/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Thirty-Four: Of Grindr and Meat Grinder Relax to these enchanted beats while reading and working out the math problem for a fuller experience. Or cower in fear of them, if you&amp;rsquo;ve played Terraria
Jack and his friends now come upon a lovely, wooded forest. Pixies play in the puddles, alicorns nibble at the grass, and rainbows grace the sky.
&amp;ldquo;Wait a cotton - pickin minute!&amp;rdquo; Exclaims Jack &amp;ldquo;This doesn&amp;rsquo;t look like Heck!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Thirty-Three: Chase&#39;s Evergaol</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/33/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/33/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Thirty-Three: Chase&amp;rsquo;s Evergaol 🍺Listen to this song while working out the math problem, and you may escape the ghastly punishment forced upon Chase by the powers that be🇩🇪
Jack and his motley crew walk on into the next circle of Heck, which they know is now home to their old friend Chase. At first, it seems very pleasant. It just looks like a normal bar, though an impeccably clean one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Thirty-Two: La Música del Diablo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/32/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/32/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Thirty-Two: La Música del Diablo 🎵 Escucha a esta canción mientras trabajas en el problema para una experiencia más completa 🎵**
Jack and his motley crew hear howling up ahead. They see a huge mass of red men with horns and pointed tails stabbing people repeatedly with pitchforks. Yet, he also sees his old friend Kaegan sitting next to them, looking extremely bored.
“Yo, bro!” he says, “Chase and I died because Philip slammed into us going 95 a few years back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Thirty-One: The Hivemind</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/31/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/31/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Thirty-One: The Hivemind 💀 Ruin your romantic relationships to the rhythm of Reddit&amp;rsquo;s Theme Song while reading and working out this math problem for a fuller experience 💀
Before the gate to the next circle of heck, there stands a morbidly obese titan, one large enough to blow the square cube law to smithereens. Upon his head is a fedora, upon his face, a neckbeard. And, upon his chest is a dirty &amp;ldquo;I FUCKING LOVE SCIENCE!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Thirty: The Parable of the Horny Man and Shaggerus</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/30/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/30/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Thirty: The Parable of the Single Man and Shaggerus Jack and his compatriots hear cries of pain coming from the circle of Heck ahead. “Like zoinks dude!&amp;quot; quoth Shaggy. “I don’t know what these dudes did, but it must’ve been pretty bad!”
Then, they finally come upon the most terrifying sight any of them hath seen thus far in Heck. Ahead of them is a boundless room &amp;ndash; stretching on in all directions to infinity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Twenty-Nine: High School Faces Eternity</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/29/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/29/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Twenty-Nine: High School Faces Eternity Jack and his friends finally reach the other side of the black sea. Chocking through the stench, they see the portion of Heck reserved for stupid teenagers. Here are imprisoned all the people who tempted Bloddy Mary, engaged in street racing, listened to Stairway to Heaven backtracked, or made love in that one porta potty off of 494.
Their punishment is to forever be imprisoned within an enlarged version of the average public high school bathroom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Twenty-Eight: Christmas Special!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/28/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/28/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Twenty-Eight: Christmas Special! A morbidly obese male ghost appears before Jack, dressed in what appear to be a dirty hospital gown. &amp;ldquo;I am the ghost of Christmas future. Grasp the side of my gown, and you shall see the shape of things to come if your quest is unsuccessful.&amp;rdquo;
Jack thinks about it for a second. &amp;ldquo;Fine, I&amp;rsquo;d like to get out of Heck for a while. It can&amp;rsquo;t be worse than this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Twenty-Seven: The Black Lake of Degnerates</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/27/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/27/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Twenty-Seven: The Black Lake of Degenerates Jack and his companions see a great black lake in front of them, on the other side of which lie the circles of Heck dedicated to degenerate high school students. At first they think it is impassable, but then they see a motorboat sitting there. Philip, who knows the way Heck works very well, says that this is how they’re meant to cross.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Twenty-Six: Of Sinners and Samurai</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/26/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/26/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Twenty-Six: Of Sinners and Samurai A Swedish heavy metal band liked this math problem so much they based a song on it. Listen to it while working the problem out for a fuller experience
As Jack and his allies come upon a large clearing, the sounds of clashing metal and yelling reach their ears. They see a legion of men dressed in traditional Japanese armor, wielding katanas and 17th century firearms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Twenty-Five: Of Goth and Goth Hunter</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/25/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Twenty-Five: Of Goth and Goth Hunter (Note 🗒️: Nevermind. I found a funny stereotype about Gen Xers)
Next up in their journey through Heck, Jack and the gang find themselves in a rainy field filled with the sound of terrible wailing. There is a huge fence, separating those on one side of the field from the other. On one side, there are a horde of souls who were once goths in life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Twenty-Four: Millennial Darn</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/24/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Twenty-Four: Millennial Darn (Note 🗒️: Gen Xers were skipped due to my inability to think of amusing stereotypes about them)
Our motley crew has moved on from the boomer fishery and made their way into the next circle of Heck. At first, it seems to be a perfectly normal town, filled with people raising children and doing their jobs. But then, Jack sees that all of the adults have tears streaming down their faces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Twenty-Three: Whatever ya say, Boomer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/23/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/23/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Twenty-Three: Whatever ya say, Boomer Having moved beyond purgatory and Limbo, Jack, Philip, and Shaggy head down into Heck itself. At first, they appear to be on the side of a normal river. But then, Jack realizes that there are large, anthropomorphic fish and crawdads sitting on the shore, fishing for people swimming around in the water.
“Uh sir,” Jack asks one of them, “what’s going on?”
“Well, this is the first circle of Heck.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Twenty-Two: Enter Gigaphil</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/22/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Twenty-Two: Enter Gigaphil 💪 For a fuller experience, lift to these virile tunes while reading and working out the math problem 💪
After wading through the corn – seas of purgatory for what feels like an eternity, Jack and Shaggy finally reach Limbo. Limbo appears to be a huge, indoor gym. For a second, they think that it’s empty, but then, they hear someone deadlifting in the distance. They follow the sound until, at long last, they see a huge beast of a man there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Twenty-One: Purgatorio</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/21/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Twenty-One: Purgatorio 🌽 Shuck to these midwestern beats while working out the math problem for a fuller experience 🌽
Jack and Shaggy find themselves in purgatory, which looks identical to rural Iowa. Corn stretches in all directions as far as the eye can see.
“Like, where the zoinks are we supposed go dude?” Shaggy asks.
Queen Elizabeth II stumbles through the shoots of corn. &amp;ldquo;Tally-ho, young sir! What were you saying?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problems Nineteen and Twenty: Sandwich Man at the Bridge of Death</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/1920/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/1920/</guid>
      <description>Math Problems Nineteen and Twenty: Sandwich Man at the Bridge of Death Saint Peter hands Jack a special, nonexchangeable ID card which will let the angels know he isn’t a darned soul trying to escape Heck, and takes him to the nearest border patrol station leading to heck and purgatory.
Just ahead of him, Jack sees Shaggy. &amp;ldquo;Like zoinks dude, this is super dooper ungroovy!&amp;rdquo; he says &amp;ldquo;Scoobs must have put some gnarly edibles on my sandwich, because I just hallucinated that Saint Peter condemned my immortal soul to 10,000 years in purgatory!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Eighteen: Paradiso</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/18/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Eighteen: Paradiso 😇 Relax to these ethereal, heavenly tunes on loop while working out the math problem for a fuller experience 😇
Jack has finally gotten to the end of the tunnel of light, and now he sees the pearly gates before him. The breathtaking display of heavenly glory is only dampened by an angry-looking Middle Eastern man in a toga.
“Hey, newly deceased sinner, get ready to be judged!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Seventeen: The Passion of the Jack</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/17/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Seventeen: The Passion of the Jack 🎵 For a Fuller Experience, Jam to These Retro Tunes While Reading and Working out the Math Problem 🎵
As Bill Clinton arrives at Jack’s home, the earth begins to shake. Church bells begin to toll in the distance - a hollow, threatening sound. The sky is stained a dusky green, the color of unpaid tax dollars. The Majora’s Mask Final Hours Theme begins to play loudly, perhaps produced by some ethereal DJ studio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Sixteen: The Beginning of the End</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/16/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/16/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Sixteen: The Beginning of the End The tax man flies off into the night at a breakneck speed and passes over the horizon. Suddenly, Jack’s phone starts ringing, and he answers it.
“Jackie boy, I am Bill Clinton, and I know what you just did. I’m coming up there to learn you the right way to treat government officials.”
Bill will be unable to start driving for thirty-six hours because his attractive female intern is visiting the dry cleaners’ in his car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Fifteen: Our Hero Changes his Mind</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/15/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Fifteen: Our Hero Changes his Mind The tax man greedily snatches Jack&amp;rsquo;s check out of his hands. He turns around and scampers away, his four chins swaying like hay in the wind. But, as his blubbery hand flops onto the door knob, Jack has a change of heart. His body accelerates from a standstill to 1,373 meters per second toward the taxman. If Jack weighs 62 kilograms, how many newtons of force will he exert upon the tax man&amp;rsquo;s body when they make contact, assuming that the air exercises 15 newtons of drag on him?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Fourteen: The One Joke you Have to Make About Money in the Future</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/14/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Fourteen: The One Joke you Have to Make About Money in the Future The tax man completes the previous math problem, and Jack sighs, knowing he’s been beat. He produces a checkbook and writes away 32 trillion dollars. Granted, this isn’t an especially large amount of money nowadays. Since hyperinflation started in 2020, twenty-five years ago, every year the value of the dollar has been an eighth of what it was the year before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Thirteen: Of Triangles and Taxes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/13/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/13/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Thirteen: Of Triangles and Taxes One day, Jack walks into his bedroom to find the IRS man standing there, waiting to pounce. He says that Jack&amp;rsquo;s ex-wife owed Bill Clinton 32 trillion dollars in taxes, and that since Jack is marked as her next of kin, he has to pay up. &amp;ldquo;I know you&amp;rsquo;re the god emperor of mankind and all that jazz now,&amp;rdquo; he says, &amp;ldquo;but these are outstanding debts from before that, so you still have to pay up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Twelve: To Answer This one, we Need to Talk About Parallel Universes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/12/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Twelve: To Answer This one, we Need to Talk About Parallel Universes Jack has absorbed Jimmy Wales’ essence and become a literal god. He rules the world with an iron fist. But, there is still one thing which his heart desires, one thing which he needs. He needs to finally take revenge on his ex - wife. He must make her pay for what she did to him. Jack couldn’t find any information about her whereabouts, so he captured her family and forced them to watch the Bee Movie until they told him where she was.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intermission Two: Jack&#39;s Revenge</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/12-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/12-5/</guid>
      <description>Intermission Two: Jack&amp;rsquo;s Revenge Jack backward long jumps many times, and then he stops. All of the force hits him immediately. He sees the parallel universes laid out before him and is aware of his traversing them. Then, a second later, he is on the ground in another world.
Jack feels in his bones that his ex wife is close. After just a few minutes of searching, he sees her: his nemesis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intermission One: The Clash of the Gods</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/115/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/115/</guid>
      <description>Intermission One: The Clash of the Gods The Grim Reaper’s flying Hearse parks in front of Jack. Death himself climbs out of the car and stands before our hero, ready to rip his soul from his body. But, something stays the reaper&amp;rsquo;s scythe. He does not speak, yet Jack hears his voice echoing inside of his head, somehow &amp;ndash; a strange, grating sound, like the slamming of coffin lids.
Aʀᴛ ᴛʜᴏᴜ ʜᴇ ᴡʜᴏ ʀᴇʙᴇʟʟᴇᴛʜ ᴀɢᴀɪɴsᴛ Jɪᴍᴍʏ Wᴀʟᴇs?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Eleven : The End of the Road</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/11/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Eleven: The End of the Road The woman accepts Jimmy Wales into her heart as her Lord and Savior and walks away. Suddenly, Jack gets a text on his phone from Jimmy Wales.
&amp;ldquo;You are doing well, son, you have proved yourself to me. Your Wikipedia article shall be stared and featured in rewards for your service.
&amp;ldquo;But, I have a mission for you. Accept, and I shall give you glory beyond your wildest dreams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Ten: Our Hero Leads a Wayward Fornicator to Faith in Jimmy Wales</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/10/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Ten: Our Hero Leads a Wayward Fornicator to Faith in Jimmy Wales Jack meets a half - naked woman from the University of California Santa Barbra, premiere party school of the United States. Before Jack even opens his mouth, she offers to have sex with him. Jack wants to very badly, but he knows he must remain chaste for Jimmy Wales.
&amp;ldquo;Why do you let dirty men lust over you day after day?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Problema de Matemáticas Nueve: Jack Aprende Español...Despacito</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/9/</guid>
      <description>Problema de Matemáticas Nueve: Jack Aprende Español &amp;hellip; Despacito Jack travels through Chase&amp;rsquo;s tunnel for a long time, eventually escaping to Mazatlán, Mexico. But, when he exits the tunnel, he sees what he wants. He sees what he needs. He sees a drug dealer passing out heroin. The temptation is too strong for Jack. Impulsively, almost instinctively, Jack moves toward him and asks for drugs.
&amp;ldquo;¡No hablo ingles!&amp;rdquo; responds the other man, quién es totalmente hispanoablante.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem 8: Ah, for just one time, I would take the Secret Passage, to Find the Hand of Chaser Reading Down to Mexico</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/8/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Eight: Ah, for Just One Time, I Would Take the Secret Passage, to Find the Hand of Chaser Reaching Down to Mexico Jack asks Chase if he can help him escape the Men in Black. Chase offers to let Jack escape down the secret tunnel he uses to traffic fursuits from Mazatlán, Mexico to Denver, Colorado.
If Denver is 1142 miles away from Mazatlán, and if Chase&amp;rsquo;s lover dug through five miles of dirt a week, how many days did it take for the tunnel to be completed?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Seven: The Chase and the Xbox</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/7/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Seven: The Chase and the Xbox Jack arrives at his buddy Chase&amp;rsquo;s house. He knocks on the door, and Chase welcomes Jack into his home. Chase and his lover feed Jack dinner, and Jack happens to look at a computer that is open to Chase&amp;rsquo;s Xbox account. Jack&amp;rsquo;s old pal has spent 134,275 Hours playing Call of Duty.
If it has been 20 years since Chase first picked up Call of Duty, what fraction of that time has he spent playing it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Six: Jack Hits the Road</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/6/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Six: Jack Hits the Road The Grim Reaper checked Jack&amp;rsquo;s Wikipedia page just after Jimmy Wales edited it. Thus, he let Jack escape his bloody scythe. The prison faculty still thought that he was dead, though, so they took him to the morgue. Jack wakes up on the autopsy table five hours later and sees a lab aid with his back turned, apparently preparing to cut him open. Jacks takes great offense at this, so he sneaks up on this sorry fellow and knocks him unconscious, robbing him of his car keys and fancy lab coat in the process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Five: Enter the Grim Reaper</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/5/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Five: Enter the Grim Reaper Jack knows what he has to do. He feels in his bones that Jimmy Wales is on his side. He knows, through a burning in his bosom, that Jimmy Wales will help him get revenge on his ex-wife. He&amp;rsquo;s just got to get this Tyrone character to donate money to Wikipedia. Jack eventually finds Tyrone and implores him to give Jimbo money, reminding him of all the lazy college students &amp;amp; malnourished Somali kids who rely on it for information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Four: Enter Jimbo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/4/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Four: Enter Jimbo Jack hates it in prison. He has nothing to eat but stale peanut butter sandwiches and no one to talk but the guard outside his cell, who keeps going on about how people in some place Jack&amp;rsquo;s never heard of have curved swords. Jack can’t feel anything but a searing hatred for his ex-wife. It’s all because of her that he&amp;rsquo;s in here. She was the one who used reverse psychology to get him to use heroin and steal his mother’s wedding ring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Three: In the Criminal Justice System, Copyright Violations are Considered Especially Heinous</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/3/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Three: In the Criminal Justice System, Copyright Violations are Considered Especially Heinous As it happens, one of the games Jack pirated contained a single sprite ripped from a Nintendo game. As soon as Shigeru Miyamoto was made aware of this vicious felony, he dispatched Nintendo&amp;rsquo;s elite legal goons to deal with the young scoundrel. They quickly capture Jack and have him hauled before a grand jury to stand trial for his crimes against God, nature, and humanity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Two: Piracy is not a Victimless Crime</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/2/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem Two: Piracy is not a Victimless Crime Jack opens a site for pirating video games. After a game comes out, it takes Jack five hours to crack the game and three hours to load the necessary ransomware onto it. If Jack pirates five games a week and will get a thousand dollars from every piece of ransomeware someone downloads, how many dollars will he make an in one week if six people download games from his site every hour?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem One: Humble Beginnings</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/humor/math/1/</guid>
      <description>Math Problem One: Humble Beginnings Jack steals his mother&amp;rsquo;s wedding ring and auctions it on eBay to pay for his heroin addiction. Every five minutes, the taking price goes up by 100 dollars. If this goes on for two and a half hours, how much money will Jack get? If Jack can buy a gram of heroin for 120 dollars, and he consumes five grams of heroin every day, how long will be be able to maintain his drug addiction?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>